{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question":"audio_cat.mp3",
      "answer1": "Bird",
      "answer2": "Cat",
      "answer3": "Mouse",
      "answer4": "Dog",
      "correct": "Cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "audio_violin.mp3",
      "answer1": "Guitar",
      "answer2": "Piano",
      "answer3": "Trumpet",
      "answer4": "Violin",
      "correct": "Violin"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_cow.mp3",
      "answer1": "Chicken",
      "answer2": "Horse",
      "answer3": "Cow",
      "answer4": "Duck",
      "correct": "Cow"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_piano.mp3",
      "answer1": "Violin",
      "answer2": "Trumpet",
      "answer3": "Piano",
      "answer4": "Guitar",
      "correct": "Piano"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_trumpet.mp3",
      "answer1": "Piano",
      "answer2": "Guitar",
      "answer3": "Violin",
      "answer4": "Trumpet",
      "correct": "Trumpet"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_horse.mp3",
      "answer1": "Horse",
      "answer2": "Duck",
      "answer3": "Chicken",
      "answer4": "Cow",
      "correct": "Horse"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_duck.mp3",
      "answer1": "Goat",
      "answer2": "Duck",
      "answer3": "Dog",
      "answer4": "Chicken",
      "correct": "Duck"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_guitar.mp3",
      "answer1": "Piano",
      "answer2": "Guitar",
      "answer3": "Violin",
      "answer4": "Trumpet",
      "correct": "Guitar"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_goat.mp3",
      "answer1": "Chicken",
      "answer2": "Duck",
      "answer3": "Goat",
      "answer4": "Dog",
      "correct": "Goat"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_chicken.mp3",
      "answer1": "Goat",
      "answer2": "Dog",
      "answer3": "Duck",
      "answer4": "Chicken",
      "correct": "Chicken"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_dog.mp3",
      "answer1": "Chicken",
      "answer2": "Duck",
      "answer3": "Goat",
      "answer4": "Dog",
      "correct": "Dog"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_bird.mp3",
      "answer1": "Mouse",
      "answer2": "Cat",
      "answer3": "Bird",
      "answer4": "Dog",
      "correct": "Bird"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_monkey.mp3",
      "answer1": "Elephant",
      "answer2": "Monkey",
      "answer3": "Snake",
      "answer4": "Mouse",
      "correct": "Monkey"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_elephant.mp3",
      "answer1": "Snake",
      "answer2": "Elephant",
      "answer3": "Mouse",
      "answer4": "Monkey",
      "correct": "Elephant"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_horn.mp3",
      "answer1": "Car Horn",
      "answer2": "Train Horn",
      "answer3": "Ship Horn",
      "answer4": "Bike Horn",
      "correct": "Car Horn"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_thunder.mp3",
      "answer1": "Rain",
      "answer2": "Crickets",
      "answer3": "Thunder",
      "answer4": "Wind",
      "correct": "Thunder"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_doorbell.mp3",
      "answer1": "Doorbell",
      "answer2": "Alarm Clock",
      "answer3": "School Bell",
      "answer4": "Boxing Bell",
      "correct": "Doorbell"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_school.mp3",
      "answer1": "Alarm Clock",
      "answer2": "Boxing Bell",
      "answer3": "Doorbell",
      "answer4": "School Bell",
      "correct": "School Bell"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_lion.mp3",
      "answer1": "Cat",
      "answer2": "Lion",
      "answer3": "Monkey",
      "answer4": "Owl",
      "correct": "Lion"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_blender.mp3",
      "answer1": "Blender",
      "answer2": "Hair Dryer",
      "answer3": "Vacuum Cleaner",
      "answer4": "Washing Machine",
      "correct": "Blender"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_rain.mp3",
      "answer1": "Crickets",
      "answer2": "Thunder",
      "answer3": "Rain",
      "answer4": "Wind",
      "correct": "Rain"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_fireworks.mp3",
      "answer1": "Airplane",
      "answer2": "Fireworks",
      "answer3": "Train",
      "answer4": "Thunder",
      "correct": "Fireworks"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_brush.mp3",
      "answer1": "Pouring Water",
      "answer2": "Door Knocking",
      "answer3": "Brushing Teeth",
      "answer4": "Cutting Paper",
      "correct": "Brushing Teeth"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_knock.mp3",
      "answer1": "Door Knocking",
      "answer2": "Cutting Paper",
      "answer3": "Pouring Water",
      "answer4": "Brushing Teeth",
      "correct": "Door Knocking"
    },
    {
      "question":"audio_pour.mp3",
      "answer1": "Brushing Teeth",
      "answer2": "Cutting Paper",
      "answer3": "Door Knocking",
      "answer4": "Pouring Water",
      "correct": "Pouring Water"
    }
  ]
}
